Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: November 2016

Apply Me Inc. (“Apply.me” or “we”) respect the privacy of its customers and visitors (“you”) and are committed to maintaining the privacy and confidentiality of your information including your personal data (collectively, “information”). Your “personal data” means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, e-mail address, credit card information for account set-up and billing, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. By visiting our website and/or using our services, you accept our privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy.

1\. Information We Collect
--------------------------

We collect your information as follows:

1.1 Information that You Provide Us. We collect any information you enter on our website or through your use of the Services or that you otherwise provide us (via chat, telephone calls, emails, online forms, etc.). This information may include identifying information such as your name, address, phone number, email address and information on services ordered. We may also collect other information from you, such as essays, scholastic information, and information regarding your education and interests, and we may also take your photograph or a video of you. We may ask you to provide your credit card or other financial account information to enable us to charge your account when you purchase products or services from us.

1.2 Information that is Collected Automatically. We collect certain types of information when you interact with us. This information may include IP address, location, email address, hardware settings, the browser you used to visit our site, system crashes, time and duration of your connection, run time information about the state of your virtual machine for example: uptime, CPU, network and disk utilization (R/W), etc.

1.3 Cookies. We use cookies and similar technologies for various reasons, such as to keep track of your activities on our website, to recognize return visitors, and to track our promotions. If you choose to provide personally identifiable information to us, then this information may be linked to data stored in the relevant cookie. Some third parties that advertise on our website also use cookies and similar techologies. Please note that this privacy policy does not cover how third parties use their cookies. You may choose to have your browser reject some or all cookies.

1.4 Information. We May Obtain from Third Party Partners and Social Media. We may receive information, including personal data, about you from Third Party Partners or social media. We may add information provided to us about you from our Third Party Partners or social media to information that we have already collected from you.

“Third Party Partners” means third parties, including without limitation scholarship sponsors, scholarship providers, tutoring and essay writers, providers of college placement services, providers of student loans, and data resellers.

1.5 Opting-Out. You can decide at any time to not provide us with any further information about yourself by clicking [here](mailto:contact@apply.me) and closing your account with us and ceasing to visit our website.

2\. How We Use Your Information
-------------------------------

2.1 Use of Your Information. We use your information only for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may directly or indirectly (through our affiliates, subcontractors, representatives and agents (which may include Third Party Partners)) use your information (regardless of whether such information is provided by you actively, or collected by us or by a Third Party Partner) to offer and provide our products and services (including by way of example, to create, maintain, secure and close your account with us including your Apply.me personalized email address, to identify you as a user in our system, to respond to your communications, to solicit feedback, to send promotional communications such as newsletters, to send upgrades and offers related to our products and services, to improve and develop our products and services, to maintain our website, and to help prevent spam, fraud and abuse), for our processing, marketing and remarketing purposes, and for the processing, marketing and other commercialization purposes of our Third Party Partners.

2.2 Unsubscribing. You may choose at any time to unsubscribe from receiving our post and email notifications and our newsletters by sending us an email to [unsubscribe@apply.me](mailto:unsubscribe@apply.me), and from our notifications by land line, mobile phone, cellular phone or text message (including internet-to-phone text message), by revoking your consent through any reasonable means at any time.

3\. Disclosure of Your Information
----------------------------------

3.1 To whom we disclose your Information, including your Personal Data. We may disclose your information, including your personal data, without your prior written consent, as follows: (i) to our affiliates, subcontractors, representatives and agents (which may include Third Party Partners), including but not limited to scholarship providers and payment processors, in connection with the provision of our products or services to you, (ii) to our remarketers in connection with remarketing services provided by our remarketers to us, such as target advertising on other sites or applications based on your online activity, (iii) to Third Party Partners for such Third Party Partners’ processing, marketing and other commercialization purposes, (iv) where we in good faith believe it is required by applicable law, court order, or by a governmental, administrative, or law enforcement authority, (v) to an acquirer of all or part of our company or our business, (vi) where we in good faith believe it is necessary in order to protect our safety or rights, or those of a third party, including but not limited to in connection with fraud detection or prevention, or security or technical issues, or (vii) where we in good faith believe it is necessary in order to enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

We will not disclose your information, including your personal information, to any third party or for any reason except for those listed above (as may be amended from time to time in our sole discretion upon an amendment of this Privacy Policy pursuant to Section 8 below) unless we have received your express written consent to such disclosure.

3.2 Third Party Privacy Policies. Upon your information being shared with our affiliate, subcontractor, representative, agent, remarketer or Third Party Partner pursuant to Section 3.1 above, we will treat your information according to the terms of our Privacy Policy, and the relevant affiliate, subcontractor, representative, agent, remarketer or Third Party Partner will treat your information according to the terms of its own privacy policy.

3.3 Third-Party Opting Out. If we have already disclosed your information to any third party, you will need to be in direct contact with that third party in connection with your concern, question, request or demand in connection with such third party’s use or disclosure of your personal information.

Third-party remarketers, including Google, AdRoll and Facebook use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). In addition, you can opt out of other third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). To find out more about how Google uses any data it collects please visit [Google Privacy & Principals](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You can opt out of receiving targeted advertisements from AdRoll by visiting the NAI website opt-out page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or the DAA opt-out page at [http://www.aboutads.info/](http://www.aboutads.info/)

4\. Information Security
------------------------

We implement commercially reasonable industry-standard security measures designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of your information, including encryption, firewalls, and access controls. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. Although we make good faith efforts to store your information in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee security. You understand and agree that all information collected through the website and the products and services that we provide is at your own risk and is subject to the provisions and disclaimers of both this Privacy Policy and our Customer Agreement.

5\. Inquiries or Complaints
---------------------------

If you have an inquiry or complaint about this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact us at [inquiries@apply.me](mailto:inquiries@apply.me).

6\. Links to Other Sites
------------------------

Our website contains links to external websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies before submitting your information.

7\. Contact Us; Removal
-----------------------

If you would like to contact us in connection with our Privacy Policy, including to request deletion of your information that is stored on our systems, please send an email to [inquiries@apply.me](mailto:inquiries@apply.me) detailing your request. If you are a minor, you may request that we remove any content you have posted from our website, products services by writing us at [inquiries@apply.me](mailto:inquiries@apply.me). Please note that any removal process does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, and, unless removal is otherwise required by applicable law, content or information related to your acceptance of a scholarship will not be subject to removal.

8\. Updates
-----------

From time to time, we may update our Privacy Policy, and your continued use of our website or our products services will signify your express agreement to such updated Privacy Policy. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on our website, and in some cases, in our sole discretion, we may notify you by email. You agree to accept posting of a revised Privacy Policy electronically on the website as actual notice to you. We encourage you to periodically check to review our Privacy Policy for updates.

Search

Search

Recent Posts
------------

Recent Comments
---------------

No comments to show.

Copyright - OceanWP Theme by OceanWP
